[
    {
        "question": "😈🗡",
        "answer": "Demon Slayer"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐰👧👨‍👧",
        "answer": "Bunny Girl Senpai"
    },
    {
        "question": "💀📃",
        "answer": "Death Note"
    },
    {
        "question": "1⃣️🧩",
        "answer": "One Piece"
    },
    {
        "question": "1⃣️👊👨",
        "answer": "One Punch Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏹❌🏹",
        "answer": "Hunter X Hunter"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐲🔮",
        "answer": "Dragon Ball"
    },
    {
        "question": "😡😴🏀",
        "answer": "Slam Dunk"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦔🔵🏃🏻",
        "answer": "Sonic"
    },
    {
        "question": "🕵️💊➞👶🏻",
        "answer": "Detective Conan"
    },
    {
        "question": "🏰💨",
        "answer": "Howl's Moving Castle"
    },
    {
        "question": "💦🌎🔥🌬",
        "answer": "Avatar The Last Airbender"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎾🤴",
        "answer": "The Prince Of Tennis"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍎🧺",
        "answer": "Fruits Basket"
    },
    {
        "question": "🧚‍♀️🦎✂️➰",
        "answer": "Fairy Tail"
    },
    {
        "question": "👾🪤🔄🔴",
        "answer": "Poke mon"
    },
    {
        "question": "🛳🏊🏼‍♂️🌙",
        "answer": "Sailor Moon"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦾🦵🙏👱➞🤖",
        "answer": "Fullmetal Alchemist"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦾👶🏻",
        "answer": "Astro Boy"
    },
    {
        "question": "🦸‍♂️🦹‍♀️🏫",
        "answer": "My Hero Academia"
    }
]